我可以带人去参加 你爸妈的结婚周年派对吗？
Is it okay if I bring someone to your parents' anniversary?
-没问题 -好啊
-Sure. -Yeah.
-你要带谁去？ -派克，我们在洗衣店里认识
-Who's the guy? -Parker,we met at the cleaners.
他把浆糊放在你的外套里？
Did he put a little starch in your bloomers?
是谁说的？
Who said that?
不，但他真的很棒 他对生命非常狂热
No,he's really great,though. He has this incredible zest for life.
他把我当女王一样 但有时他当我是顽皮女孩
He treats me like a queen. Except when he treats me like a naughty girl.
我可以致词吗？
Would it be okay if I give the toast?
即使经过 他们20周年纪念日的意外后？
Even after what happened at their 20th?
-我真的很想 -希望这次妈不会嘘你
-I'd really like to. -Hopefully this time Mom won't boo you.
对，每年都是罗斯致词 他把他们都弄哭了
Yes! Every year Ross makes the toast,and it always makes them cry.
-今年我要把他们弄哭 -你不知道他们为什么最爱罗斯吗？
-This year,I'm gonna make them cry. -You wonder why Ross is their favorite?
只要罗斯一致词 大家都会哭着拍他的背
Any time Ross makes a toast,everyone cries and pats him on the back.
他们都来跟我说 “天啊，你哥哥”
And they all come up to me and say,"God,your brother."
你知道今天他们今年会怎么说吗？ “天啊，你”
You know what they're gonna say this year? "God,you."
至少有个人会哭
Well,at least one person will be crying.
我是演员 演员随时都可以哭
I'm an actor,and any actor worth his salt can cry on cue.
-真的吗？你做的到吗？ -你是在开玩笑吗？看着
-Really? You can do that? -Oh,you kidding me? Watch.
你们盯着我看 我办不到
Well,I can't do it with you guys watching me!
本集播出：马沙皮卡市
The.One.In.Massapequa
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：马修派瑞
主演：大卫修蒙
嘿
Hey.
天啊 你看起来美极了
Oh,my God. You look so fantastic.
我在来这里的路上 用我的心灵之眼想像你的模样
On my way over,I pictured you in my mind's eye.
现在我想说 “心灵之眼，你错了”
Now I'm like,"Mind's eye,you had no idea!"
-我们再来一次 -好吧
-Let's do that again! -Okay.
-你在做什么？ -我在写我的演讲稿
-What are you doing? -I'm working on my toast.
或许我该叫它 “哭泣的集会 2002”
Or as I like to call it: "Sob-fest 2002."
我等不及要看他们哭了
I cannot wait to see them cry.
那不是一般的哭泣 他们会像《母女情深》里的演员一样大哭
It's not gonna be like regular crying. It's gonna be like Terms of Endearment crying.
我要我爸妈痛哭流涕…
I'm gonna reduce my parents to sniffling,quaking masses of..
我可能还在为小时候的事 生我爸妈的气
I may have some unresolved anger from my childhood.
-你看 -是小狗
-Hey,check this out. -It's a dog.
那是只死狗
It's a dead dog.
琪琪在我高中时死掉了
Chi-Chi. She died when I was in high school.
-你要谈一只死狗？ -那个主题不错吧？
-You're talking about a dead pet? -It's good stuff,huh?
乔伊 你准备好要送我爸妈的礼物了吗？
Joey? You got a present for my parents?
为了纪念他们结婚35周年 我用他们的名字帮星星取名
In honor of their 35th anniversary,I had a star named after them.
-那真的太酷了-我还买了老年版的《爱经》（描述做爱姿势的印度古书）
}-That is so cool. -And I got Kama Sutra for the Elderly.
我想或许一样礼物就够了
You know,I think maybe the one present is enough.
-你们有多余的缎带吗？ -当然有
-Do you guys have any extra ribbon? -Sure.
你要什么？我们有蕾丝 缎子、棉布、亚麻、条纹布
What do you need? We got lace,satin,sateen,raffia,gingham,felt..
我想我的蛋蛋 应该也在这里
And I think my testicles may be in here too.
琪琪，我爱这只狗
Chi-Chi! Oh,I loved this dog.
莫妮卡当时很不安是 因为琪琪得动膝盖手术
Monica couldn't get braces because Chi-Chi needed knee surgery.
-什么？ -你是骑着它跑的两百磅重大胖子
-What? -You're the 200-pounder who rode her!
大伙们，他是派克 派克，这是…
Hey! Everybody,this is Parker. Parker,this is..
不，别告诉我，让我猜 乔伊，莫妮卡，罗斯，瑞秋…
No,don't tell me. Let me guess: Joey,Monica,Ross,Rachel..
对不起 菲比没有提过你
and I'm sorry,Phoebe didn't mention you.
钱德，我是在开玩笑 你已经是我的最爱了
Chandler,I'm kidding! Already you're my favorite.
-跟我谈谈你的事 -事实上我们该走了
-Tell me a little about yourselves. -Actually,we should get going.
典型的罗斯
Classic Ross!
瑞秋，你好漂亮，我可以吗？
Rachel,look how you glow! May I?
我想你已经不请自来了
I think you already are.
瑞秋 你体内孕育着一个小生命
Rachel,you have life growing inside you.
有什么更神奇… 一张狗照片，这是谁的狗？
Is there anything more miraculous.. A picture of a dog! Whose is this?
那是我以前养的狗 他在好几年前过世了
That's my old dog. He passed away years ago.
至少你很幸运能拥有他 汪汪，我的老朋友，汪汪
Well,at least you were lucky to have him. Bow-wow,old friend. Bow-wow.
大伙们，我们真的该走了
You guys,we really should get going.
我又犯了多话的老毛病
There I go again,my catch phrase.
-派对在哪里举行？ -在马沙皮卡
-So where's the party? -It's in Massapequa.
马沙皮卡，听起来跟魔法一样 它是美国原住民历史上的名胜吗？
Massapequa,it sounds magical. Is it steeped in Native American history?
那里有原住民帐篷形状的 艾比餐厅
Well,there is an Arby's in the shape of a tepee.
我拿了纸条，你拿了礼物吗？
I've got my notes. You got the presents?
-我拿了车钥匙 -我们要开车吗？太棒了
-I've got the car keys. -We're driving? Aces.
-他似乎是个好人 -对，我很喜欢他
-So he seems like a nice guy. -Yeah,I like him a lot.
-你想被丢下搭计程车吗？ -好吧，除非我不想去
-You want to hang back and take a cab? -Okay,otherwise I'm not going.
-嘿，妈妈 -这个派对真的很棒
-Hey,Mom. -This is such a great party!
35年，太棒了 你们有什么至理名言吗？
Thirty-five years. Impressive. Do you have any pearls of wisdom?
-杰克 -为什么食物上要插着牙签？
-Jack? -Why serve food on such a sharp stick?
那是个好问题，爸爸 那是个好问题
It's a good question,Dad. It's a good question.
-恭喜你们 -谢谢，我们很兴奋
-Congratulations,you two. -Thank you,we're so excited.
还要恭喜 你们结婚了
And also,congratulations on your wedding.
-我们能跟你们谈一下吗？ -好吧
-Can we talk to you for just a moment? -Yeah.
这只是件小事
It's just a little thing.
我们觉得你们未婚生子 真的很棒…
While we think it's marvelous you're having this baby out of wedlock..
但我们的朋友没有那么开放
our friends are less open-minded.
-我们告诉他们你们结婚了 -什么？
-We told them you're married. -What?
谢谢你们愿意配合
Thanks for going along with this.
-我们得假装我们结婚了 -我为了今晚必须要掏耳朵
-We have to pretend that we're married? -I had to shave my ears.
这你至少可以做到
You can do this.
-你能相信吗？ -我知道
-Can you believe that? -I know.
如果你要掏耳朵 最好顺便挖一下鼻子
If you do the ears,you may as well take a pass at the nose.
我不想骗人 我结婚了
I don't want to have to lie about being married.
我也不想，但这是他们的派对 而且只有一晚而已
I don't either. But it's their party,and it's one night.
我们不必说谎 我们只要不说话
We don't have to lie. We won't talk.
如果有人提起 我们只要微笑点头…
If it comes up,we'll smile,we'll nod along..
-罗斯 -瑞秋
-Ross? -Rachel?
嗨，丽莎阿姨，丹姨父
Hi,Aunt Lisa. Uncle Dan.
恭喜你们怀孕 还结了婚
Congratulations on the baby and on the wedding.
-这是个好开始 -你们婚后还好吧？
-Here's something to start you out. -How's marriage treating you?
-不可思议，太棒了 -我们喜欢结婚
-Unbelievable. It's great! -We love marriage.
待会见
We'll see you later.
-嘿 -嗨
-Hey! -Hi!
莫妮卡 你的驾驶技术太棒了
Can I just say,Monica,that your driving is exquisite.
谢谢，我之前说过 我只是没有越线…
Thanks. Like I said before,I pretty much just stayed in the lines..
试着不要撞到人
and tried not to hit anybody.
好漂亮的地方 好棒的夜晚
What a beautiful place. What a great night.
我得告诉你们 能跟你们一起在C宴会厅…
I have to tell you,being here with all of you in Event Room C..
我觉得好幸运 想想这里曾有过的美好时光
I feel so lucky. Think of the good times that happened here.
生日，毕业舞会 犹太教戒规，酒后的喧哗
The birthdays,the proms,the mitzvahs,both bar and bat!
它们都比不上今晚 我不想忘了它
None will compare with tonight. I don't want to forget it.
我想在我心里 帮你们拍张照，喀
It's like I want to take a mental picture of you all. Click.
我想闪光灯没亮
I don't think the flash went off.
-我要去男洗手间 -我跟你一起去
-I'm gonna find the men's room. -I'll go with you.
有人躲在某个地方 拿着麻醉枪…
Somewhere there is someone with a tranquilizer gun..
跟大蝴蝶网 在找那个家伙
and a huge butterfly net looking for that man.
我也想上厕所 但我不想让他夸奖我的小弟弟
I have to go too,but I don't want him complimenting my thing.
还好我们没在车上 他发作了吗？
Glad we weren't in the car. Did he let up?
他叫长岛高速公路 是“水泥奇迹”
He called the Long lsland Expressway a "concrete miracle."
这个房间，今晚
This room. This night.
服务生，他的鞋子 我得用心拍张照片
That waiter! His shoes! I must take a mental picture!
抱歉
Sorry.
你们在取笑派克吗？
Were you guys making fun of Parker?
那得看你听到了多少
That depends,how much did you hear?
他是有点狂热 那有什么不对？
He's a little enthusiastic. What's wrong with that?
-他太过火了 -那又怎么样？我喜欢他
-It's so much. -Well,so what? I like him.
我会取笑你们的约会对象吗？ 泰格，珍妮丝，蒙娜
Do I make fun of the people you date? Tag,Janice,Mona.
不，因为朋友不会那么做 你们想知道我的想法吗？
No,because friends don't do that. Do you want my opinion?
你们的约会纪录 加起来跟人渣历史差不多
Your collective dating record reads like a who's who of human crap!
-我觉得好难过 -我知道
-I feel terrible. -I know.
蒙娜有哪里不好？
What was wrong with Mona?
-快打开 -好的，宝贝
-Open it,open it,open it. -Yeah,baby!
我们不知道你们结婚了
So we never got to hear about your wedding.
-我们很讶异我们没有被邀请 -不，婚礼的规模很小
-We were surprised we weren't invited. -No,it was a small wedding.
但它很美 规模很小但很特别
But it was beautiful. It was small,but kind of spectacular.
-你们在哪里举行婚礼？ -在巴贝多（加勒比海小岛）悬崖上的黄昏婚礼
-Where did you have it? -On a cliff in Barbados,at sunset.
我走上红毯时 史提夫汪达（黑人盲人歌手）唱着《她真美》
And Stevie Wonder sang " lsn't She Lovely" as I walked down the aisle.
-史提夫是我们家的朋友 -天啊，那真的是太棒了
-Stevie's a family friend. -Oh,my God. That's amazing.
-我想看照片 -对，我也是
-I'd love to see pictures. -Yeah,so would I.
你们不会相信 安妮・莱博维茨（著名女摄影师）忘了装底片
You wouldn't think Annie Liebowitz would forget to put film in the camera.
失陪一下
Would you excuse us for a second?
-你在做什么？ -什么？那可能是我唯一一场婚礼
-What are you doing? -What? This may be my only wedding.
-我希望它真的很棒 -好吧
-And I want it to be amazing. -Okay.
-或许我该骑着哈雷机车入场 -罗斯，我们得编得很像真的
-Maybe I rode in on a Harley. -Ross,it has to be realistic.
你好吗？你似乎很安静
Say,are you okay? You seem kind of quiet.
-我没事，我跟你在一起 -我跟你在一起，真的是太棒了
-No,I'm fine. I'm great. I'm with you. -And I'm with you. What a great time!
看看这个送盘器
Look at this plate bouncy thing.
这是个天才发明 解决了端盘子的问题
What an inspired solution to man's plate-dispensing problems.
-生蚝，让我来喂你 -你不必那么做
Oysters! Let me feed you. That's not necessary.
-拜托 -我不吃…
-Please? -I don't eat..
-你不吃的话我绝不罢休 -好吧
-I won't quit until you try one. -Okay,fine.
-很好 -它们是什么味道？我从来没吃过
-Good. -What're they like? I've never had one.
-试试看 -它们看起来好奇怪
-Try one. -They look too weird.
我知道
I know,I know.
听着，你的家人 真的开始喜欢我
Listen,your family is really starting to warm up to me.
你刚刚吻的是承办酒席的
You just kissed the caterer.
-你在做什么？ -准备我的演讲
-What are you doing? -Going over my toast.
会让他们好好的吓一跳
Those two will never know what hit'em
我等不及了，他们会痛哭流涕 他们会喘不过气来
I can't wait. They'll cry so hard,they'll be fighting for breath.
如果你要的话 我可以抓住他们，让你…
If you want to,I could just hold them down and you could just..
我戴着蕾丝婚纱 它是由比利时瞎修女织的
And my veil was lace,made by blind Belgian nuns.
-瞎眼？ -本来不是的，但这工作非常伤眼力
-Blind? -Not at first,but it's intricate work.
她们说虽然她们眼睛瞎了 但这还是很值得的
They said even though they lost their sight,it was worth it.
-我敢说你看起来很漂亮 -我不知道
-I bet you looked beautiful. -Well,I don't know.
但有些宾客说 我看起来像飞天天使
But there were some people that said I looked like a floating angel.
-你怎么求婚的？ -对，那是个很棒的故事
-How did you propose? -Oh,yeah,that's a great story.
事实上 我带她去看太阳系模型展
Well,actually,I took her to the planetarium.
我们在那里第一次约会
That's where we had our first date.
我在房里 放满了她最喜欢的百合花
I had the room filled with lilies,her favorite flower.
-那真的太棒了 -我还想听
-That is so sweet! -I want to hear the rest!
弗雷德・阿斯泰尔（电影及舞台剧演员）唱着 《你今晚的样子》…
Then Fred Astaire singing,"The Way You Look Tonight" came on..
灯光熄了，我单脚跪下
the lights came down,I got on one knee..
圆顶另一端 在群星间写着
and written across the dome,in the stars,were the words:
“你愿意嫁给我吗？”
"Will you marry me?"
戒指有我的拳头那么大
And the ring was the size of my fist.
菲比，听着…
Hey,Phoebe? Look..
我想道歉，好吗？ 我们太坏了
I want to apologize. Okay? We were being jerks.
-派克人很好，我想多了解他 -你最好快去找他
-Parker's nice,I'd like to know him. -You better do it now.
-为什么？ -因为我要杀了他
-Why? -Because I'm gonna kill him.
-什么？ -他对所有事都太兴奋了
-What? -He's too excited about everything.
我也很喜欢生命 但这是盖勒夫妇结婚35周年派对
I'm all for living,but this is the Gellers' 35th anniversary.
就算我们扯平了 这个派对烂透了
Let's call a spade a spade. This party stinks.
我真的觉得无聊到极点
I'm having the worst time.
大家排队拿食物 我拿到盘子时…
There was a line for the buffet,and when I got to the plates..
踩到一大坨鼻涕滑倒
I slipped on a giant booger.
你确定那不是生蚝吗？
Are you sure it wasn't an oyster?
有可能，我没看
It could've been. I didn't look at it.
我把它抹在钱德的外套上 拔腿就溜
I wiped it on Chandler's coat and got the hell out.
我还以为他是个好人 我对他真的很期待
I thought he was a great guy. I was so excited about him.
嘿，你应该对他充满期待
Well,hey,you should be excited about him.
他没有什么不好的
There's nothing wrong with him.
-真的吗？ -对，你知道吗？
-You think? -Yeah,know what?
-我们太悲观了 -你说的对
-We were all just being too negative. -You're right.
他只是在拥抱生命 我们可以跟派克学习
He's just embracing life. We could all stand to be more like Parker.
你知道吗？我就跟他一样 我是个乐观的人
You know what? I'm like him! I'm a positive person!
-事实上你说的对 -那是什么？
-Actually,you have an edge. -What's that?
-是派克 -看，兔子舞
-Oh,it's Parker! -Look,the Bunny Hop!
-我喜欢 -是吗？
-Oh,I love it! -You do?
你在开玩笑吗？ 跟着音乐学动物跳舞？来吧
Are you kidding? People acting like animals to music? Come on!
好吧，该致词了
Okay,it's time for the toast.
我知道一向都是由罗斯来致词 但今年由我来
I know normally Ross gives the toast,but this year I'll do it.
不，它真的很棒
No,it's gonna be great. Really.
好的
Okay.
妈，爸，我结婚时…
Mom,Dad,when I got married..
我很确定 我要以你们为榜样
the thing that made me sure I could do it was the example you two set.
为了那一点及其他事 我要感谢你们
For that,and other things,I want to thank you.
我想或许我不常那么说…
I know I probably don't say it enough..
但我爱你们
but I love you.
我转头一看，悲伤地想起 没办法出席的人
When I look around,I'm saddened by the thought of those who could not be here.
我亲爱的外婆 她真的很想来
Nana,my beloved grandmother,who would so want to be here.
但她来不了…
But she can't..
因为她死了
because she's dead.
还有我们的狗琪琪
As is our dog,Chi-Chi.
你们看它多可爱…那是以前的事了
I mean,look how cute she is.. was.
帮我一个忙 请把这个传给我爸妈
Do me a favor,pass this to my parents.
记住它死了，好吗？ 它跟外婆都死了
Remember she's dead,okay? Her and Nana,gone.
哇
Wow!
有谁记得…
Does anybody remember when..
德博拉・温格在《母女情深》中得跟她的孩子们说再见的样子？
Debra Winger had to say goodbye to her children in Terms of Endearment?
你们没看过？
Didn't see that?
没有人是影迷？
No movie fans?!
你们想听些悲伤的事吗？
You want to hear something sad?
我在《60分钟》 看到罗马尼亚孤儿院的报导…
I was watching a 60 Minutes piece on orphans in Romania..
他们遭到抛弃 无法被爱
who have been so neglected that they were incapable of love.
你们的心都是石头做的
You people are made of stone!
敬爸妈，随便啦
Here's to Mom and Dad. Whatever!
谢谢莫妮卡 那真的是太有趣了
Thank you,Monica. That was interesting.
-那真的很有趣吧？杰克 -为什么我不记得这只狗？
-Wasn't it interesting,Jack? -Why don't I remember this dog?
罗斯，你为什么不为我们致词？
Ross? Why don't you give us your toast now?
不，妈 今年轮到莫妮卡了
Oh,no,Mom. It's just Monica this year.
在我们35周年派对上 你不致词吗？
You're not saying anything? On our 35th wedding anniversary?
当然不是
No,of course.
大伙们，我只是想…
Everybody? I just wanted to say..
代表我的新娘瑞秋…
on behalf of my new bride,Rachel..
跟我自己说…
and myself,that if..
如果我们结婚35年后 有你们一半幸福…
if in 35 years,we're half as happy as you guys are..
我们会觉得 自己是全世界最幸运的人
we'll count ourselves the luckiest people in the world.
罗斯
Oh,Ross.
希望外婆还活着 听到罗斯的致词
I just wish Nana were alive to hear Ross' toast.
天啊 这个走廊的灯光真漂亮
My God,what a fantastically well-lit hallway.
你需要喝点东西吗？ 譬如水跟镇静剂
Can I get you something to drink,like a water and Valium?
我得说这间公寓 它…我不知道该怎么形容
I must say,this apartment,it's.. there are no words.
-谢天谢地 -它是个天堂
-Thank God. -It's a haven.
-位于三楼的天堂，现代伊甸园 -我知道，我了解
-A third-floor paradise,a modern Eden. -Yeah,I know,I know. Gotcha.
听着，我们为什么不坐下来放轻松 安静地彼此依偎
Listen,why don't we just sit and relax,just be with each other quietly.
听起来很不错
That sounds great.
这是我坐过 最舒服的沙发
This is the most comfortable couch I've ever sat on.
我们试试别的点子 我们来玩游戏
Let's try something. Let's play a game.
-我喜欢玩游戏 -太棒了
-I love games. -Shocking.
我们来玩…
Let's play the game of..
谁能最久不说话的游戏
who can stay quiet the longest.
或层层叠
Or Jenga.
我们先玩这个 记住，先说话的人就输了
Let's play this one first,and remember,whoever talks first loses.
-我输了，现在来玩层层叠 -我的天啊
-I lose,now Jenga. -Oh,my God.
-哪里不对劲吗？ -你知道什么是“不对劲”吗？
-Is something wrong? -You know the word "wrong"?
一切不是美好又神奇吗？
Everything isn't perfect or magical?
一切不是都在 发光发亮吗？
Everything isn't aglow with the light of fairies?
那只是刹车灯，派克
They were just brake lights,Parker!
对不起，我美化了塞车
Excuse me for putting a good spin on a traffic jam.
你不必美化所有事
You don't have to put a good spin on everything!
-抱歉，我是个乐观的人 -不，我是个乐观的人
-I'm sorry. I'm a positive person. -No,I'm a positive person.
你像吃了抗忧郁药的圣诞老人
You are like Santa Claus on Prozac.
在迪士尼乐园做爱
At Disneyland,getting laid!
你要我悲观吗？ 你要我不快乐吗？
You want me to be negative? You want me to be less happy?
非常不快乐
Much less happy.
好吧，引用罗斯的话 “我最好走了”
Fine. Well,then to quote Ross,"I better be going."
再见
So long!
别让“全世界最棒的门” 在你出去时打到你的屁股了
Don't let the "best door in the world" hit you in the ass on your way out.
这是你一辈子 吵过最不可思议的架吧？
Isn't this the most incredible fight you've had in your life?
你坐在车斗里 我们从婚礼现场走到接待处
We could've gone from the ceremony to the reception with you in the sidecar.
那行不通
It just isn't feasible.
但鸽子停在你的戒指上 就没有问题
But a dove placing the ring on your finger would've been no problem.
-跟你结婚真的太棒了 -对，这四百块真好赚
-It was fun being married to you. -Yeah,and it was an easy 400 bucks.
-罗斯，我能问你一件事吗？ -好吧
-Okay,Ross,can I ask you something? -Yeah.
-在天文馆求婚？ -我知道，那太蠢了
-That proposal at the planetarium? -I know,I know. It was stupid.
你在开玩笑吗？ 有百合花、歌跟星星？
Are you kidding? With the lilies,and the song and the stars?
那真的是太棒了 你是随便编的吗？
It was really wonderful. Did you just make that up?
我们交往时 我想过要那么做
I thought of it when we were going out.
是我想跟你求婚的样子
That's how I imagined I would ask you to marry me.
哇
Wow.
要拒绝你一定很难
Well,that would've been very hard to say no to.
还好我没有那么做 听起来那会是个昂贵的婚礼
It's a good thing I didn't do it,it sounds like a very expensive wedding.
-好吧，晚安 -晚安
-Okay,good night. -Good night.
即使车斗有挡风玻璃 不弄乱你的头发也不行吗？
Even if the sidecar had a windscreen to protect your hair?
-我会考虑的 -我已经满足了
-I will think about it. -That's all I'm asking.
好吧，够了，我放弃了
Okay,that's it. I give up.
在爸妈的40周年派对上 由你来致词
At Mom and Dad's 40th anniversary,you give the speech.
我不了解他们为什么没哭 你的致词真感人
You know,I don't understand why they didn't cry.
-好了 -你说的关于真爱的事？
-Come on. -That stuff you said about true love?
你说的对 我们从爸妈那里学到了很多
You were right. We did learn a lot from Mom and Dad.
琪琪在照片上 调皮地笑着
That picture of Chi-Chi with her mischievous grin.
还有外婆那一段 她真的会很想去参加
And what you said about Nana? Yeah,she really would've wanted to be there.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
我想她去了
I think she was.
天啊，罗斯 你是怎么办到的？
Oh,good God,Ross,how the hell do you do it?